Berliner Gramophone Disc Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Recordings, Series I
  - Che Faro seiza [unintelligible]; Cantata dal Sig Galare; 54758, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667890)
    Disc No. 53176
  - Stude la vamja; Cantata dalla sigma Galan; 53174, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667908)
    Disc No. 53174
  - Mi Chiarinano Mimi; Cantata dalla Sig Adami; 53171, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520775)
    Disc No. 53171
  - Vaga donna illusbreetcana; 53170, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667916)
    Disc No. 53170
  - Rondo Idol Piggio; Cantata dalla Sig Galan; 53169, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667924)
    Disc No. 53169
  - Faust; Bice Adami; 53165X, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520783)
    Disc No. 53165X
  - Klaaglied (Paljas) - gesongen door - H. Desire Pauwels - Amsterdam, undated; 1 (Box 740, Item barcode 39002126523670)
    Disc No. 92070. Dutch - Tenor.
  - Siciliana (Cavalleria Rusticana) - gezongen door - H. Desire Pauwels - Amsterdam, undated; 1 (Box 740, Item barcode 39002126523688)
    Disc No. 92069. Dutch - Tenor.
  - Duet euit Mascotta - gezongen door - Mvr. Buderman v. Dyk en J.A.F. Grootveld - Amsterdam, undated; 1 (Box 740, Item barcode 39002126523696)
    Disc No. 94000. Dutch - Duet.
  - The Palms Paure: Cornet Solo by W. Paris Chambers, 1887 November 8; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521336)
    Disc No. 219
  - Terra: The Holy City, 1887 November 8; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521344)
    Disc No. 986-V
  - Just One Girl by Mr. J.W. Myers, 1934; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521351)
    Disc No. 1934 Z
  - Gounod's Serenade: Saxophone Solo by Mons. Jean Moeremans of Sousa's Band, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521369)
    Disc No. 3904 Z
  - Arthur Pryor: Lion du Bal by The Members of Sousa's Band, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521377)
    Disc No. 0177A
  - Dudley Manager: Lead Kindly Light Sung By Haydn Quartette, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521385)
    Disc No. 42652
  - A Talk By Cal Stewart: The Yankee Comedian; No. 2, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521401)
    Disc No. 6001
  - Otto Schreilier: March From The Fortune Teller By Victor Herbert's 22nd Rgt. Band, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521419)
    Disc No. 8001 X
  - Henry Higgins Sousa's Band: Medley Of Irish Alrs Played by Sousa's Band, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521427)
    Disc No. 8009-Z
  - SM Dudley Manager: Nearer My God to Thee Sung by The Haydn Quartet, 1899 March 25; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521435)
    Disc No. 021
  - Zigeumerweisen: Violin Solo by J. Jacobs, 1898 December 29; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521450)
    Disc No. 7906
  - Moscow Sun by Mr. Rubin, 1899 April 4; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521468)
    Disc No. 11093
  - Margarita, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521476)
    Disc No. 20061
  - Unsinn [unintelligible], undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521484)
    Disc No. 20717
  - [foreign language], undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521492)
    Disc No. 23040X
  - [foreign language], undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521500)
    Disc No. 24229
  - Le Gramophone: F. Derode Dit Par L'auteur Paris, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521518)
    Disc No. 31010
  - Sigurd: Reyer/ Odin Dieu Farouche-Chant du Bard Sung by Monsieur Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521526)
    Disc No. 32442
  - Galathee: Masse v. Venus Sun by Monsieur Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521534)
    Disc No. 32964
  - Les Joyeux Serins (Thuillier) avec siffle. Monsiur Lergeret, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521542)
    Disc No. 2-32056
  - Le Chalet (Adam): Dans Le Service De l'Autriche Sung by Monsieur Baer, Basse de l'Opera, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521559)
    Disc No. 2-32087
  - Henri VIII. Saint-Saens. Anne, Ma Bien-Aimee Sung by Monsieur Baer, Basse de l'Opera, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521567)
    Disc No. 2-32111
  - La Mascotte (Audran): Le Secret De Polichinelle Sung By Monsieur Soums, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521575)
    Disc No. 2-32114
  - Les Cloches De Corneville (Planquette)/ Je Regardais En l'Air Sung by Monsieur Soums, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521583)
    Disc No. 2-32118
  - A La Cabane Bambou (P. Marinier): Chanson Negre Sung by Monsieur Mayol, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521591)
    Disc No. 2-32137
  - Pourquoi/ Lakme Delibes Sung by Mlle Relda, 1908 August 15; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521609)
    Disc No. 33207
  - Leopold [unintelligible]: Hand in Hand, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521617)
    Disc No. 42006
  - Gustav Wasehow: Roccoco-Standehen v. Meyer-Hellmund, undated; 1 (Box 744, Item barcode 39002126521625)
    Disc No. 42210
  - Werner Alberti (Budapest) - Italia, mein Vaterland; Stradella, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521633)
    Disc No. 42311
  - Carlo Bohm (Vienna) - Ja, ja der Peter; Generalkonsul, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521641)
    Disc No. 2-42261
  - Rudolf Hofbauer (Vienna) - Was ich langst ertraumte; Gottergatte, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521658)
    Disc No. 2-42282
  - Nelly Brodtmann (Wiesbaden) - Kartenlied; Carmen, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521666)
    Disc No. 43101
  - Frau Goetze, Royal Chambermusic Singer (Berlin) - Wiegenlied von Petri, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521674)
    Disc No. 43107
  - Frau Knupfer (Berlin) - Ihr, die ihr Triebe; Figaro's Hochzeit, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521682)
    Disc No. 43118
  - Josephine Kraus (Berlin) - Lied vom sussen Madel; Das Susse Madel, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521690)
    Disc No. 43168
  - Mitzi Zwerenz (Vienna) - Gehen wir in's Chambre separee; Opernball, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521708)
    Disc No. 43187
  - Operasinger Maikki Jarnefelt and pianist Armas Jarnefelt (Helsingfors) - Meine Liebe is grun (Brahms), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521716)
    Disc No. 43379
  - Marie Knupfer-Egli, Kgl. Hofopernsangerin (Berlin); mit Orchester-Begleitung, Kapellmeister Seidler-Winkler - Letzte Rose aus Martha, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521724)
    Disc No. 2-43002
  - Gertrud Runge / Kapellmeister Seidler-Winkler (Berlin), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521732)
    Disc No. 2-43003
  - Ferruccio Corradetti (Milan), cantata from Santa Lucia, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521740)
    Disc No. 52213
  - Ottavio Prosoni (tenor) - Aida, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521757)
    Disc No. 52281
  - Carlo Caffetto, 1900 July 27; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521765)
    Disc No. 52471
  - Carlo Caffetto, 1900 July 25; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521773)
    Disc No. 52485x
  - Carlo Caffetto, 1900 July 28; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521781)
    Disc No. 52486
  - Carlo Caffetto - Pucchini, 1900 July 16; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521799)
    Disc No. 52512
  - Franchi - Donizetti, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521807)
    Disc No. 52527
  - [unclear], undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521815)
    Disc No. 52589
  - Bice Adami (soprano); Traviata, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521823)
    Disc No. 53105
  - Bice Adami (soprano); Puccini, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521831)
    Disc No. 53115
  - Signorina Grossi (soprano); Verdi, 1900 April 8; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521849)
    Disc No. 53161
  - D'Avigny; Cantalamessa, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521856)
    Disc No. 54136
  - Angelo Alfieri (mandoline with piano); Serenata Lombarda, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521864)
    Disc No. 57369
  - Senor Banquella (bass), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521872)
    Disc No. 62515
  - Senorita Mirallesi, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521880)
    Disc No. 63190
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone); Soldatgossen, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521898)
    Disc No. 72089
  - August Svensson (baritone); O min Carl Gustaf, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521906)
    Disc No. 72116
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Du gamla du fria, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521914)
    Disc No. 72124
  - August Svensson (baritone) - Storataren (72297); I unga dar (72296), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521922)
    Disc No. 72296/7
  - Neveto dal Deneverbol; Szoyer Ilonka (soprano), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521930)
    Disc No. 73019
  - Malka Bobkova (soprano) - Hubicka, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521948)
    Disc No. 73031
  - Magna Lykseth-Schjerven (soprano) - Fjorton ar tror jeg visst att jag var (73034); Kolibrisangen ur Jaguarita (73035), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521955)
    Disc No. 73034/5
  - Rosa Grunberg (soprano) - Om dagen vid mitt arbete, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521963)
    Disc No. 73065
  - Fraulein Halasz (soprano) - Lucia (Donizetti), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521971)
    Disc No. 73164
  - Oscar Bergstrom and August Svensson (baritone duet) - Nu tror jeg det kan vara tid (Glunatarne), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521989)
    Disc No. 74007
  - Nya Solist Kvartetten (quartet) - Skratta, mina barn och vanner (Bellman) (74024); Kristallen den fina (74025), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126521997)
    Disc No. 74024/5
  - Inga Berentz and Oscar Bergstrom (duet) - Den gamla mamsellens sang, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522003)
    Disc No. 74026
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Positiv Visa (Bjorn Hallden), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522011)
    Disc No. 82034
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Scalza serenade (Boccaccio), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522029)
    Disc No. 82053
  - Pasi Jaaskelainen (tenor) - a) Haa laulu; b) Paljo olen maata kulkenut, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522037)
    Disc No. 82155
  - John Forsell (baritone) - Den nalkande stormen (E.G. Geijer), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522045)
    Disc No. 82501
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Mandom, mod och morske man (Richard Dybeck), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522052)
    Disc No. 82502
  - G.A. Lund (tenor) - Svensk folkvisa, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522060)
    Disc No. 82513
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Jag ar ung (Ivar Hallstrom), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522078)
    Disc No. 82518
  - Svend Nyblom (tenor) - Aria ur operan Trubaduren, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522086)
    Disc No. 82528x
  - Oscar Bergstrom (baritone) - Min sang (Ivar Hallstrom), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522094)
    Disc No. 82529
  - Henning Malm (baritone) - Julsang (Adam), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522102)
    Disc No. 82532
  - Johannes Forsell (baritone) - Hvita Rosor (Korling), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522110)
    Disc No. 82631
  - Johannes Forsell (baritone) - Jeg elsker dig (Grieg), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522128)
    Disc No. 82632
  - August Svenson (baritone) - Sangaren paa vandring, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522136)
    Disc No. 82639
  - Johannes Forsell (baritone) - Du gamla, du friska, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522144)
    Disc No. 82633
  - Ake Wallgren (baritone) - En sangers bon (Reissiger), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522151)
    Disc No. 82642
  - Henning Malm (tenor) - Eriks sang ur Farmlanningarne, undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522169)
    Disc No. 82647
  - John Forsell (baritone) - Jag vill ut (Carl Elling), undated; 1 (Box 744a, Item barcode 39002126522177)
    Disc No. 82661
  - Vandering in Skoven (Grieg); Johanne Kragballe-Spiro (soprano), undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522185)
    Disc No. 83173
  - Fru Friis-Hjorth (soprano) - Jeg gor det aldrig mer'!, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522193)
    Disc No. 83187
  - Vahlborg Svardstrom (soprano) - Allt under himmelens faste, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522219)
    Disc No. 83208
  - Mathilda Jungstedt (mezzo-soprano) - Intet ar som vantanstiden, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522201)
    Disc No. 83250
  - Schwedissches Mannerqvartett (quartet) - Ja vi elsker, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522227)
    Disc No. 85109
  - Svensk Gluntsangare (duet) - Hvad det ar skont anda (Wennerberg), undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522235)
    Disc No. 84115
  - Oscar Bergstrom and August Svenson (duet) - En manskensnatt i stottsbacken (Wennerberg), undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522243)
    Disc No. 84119
  - Oscar Bergstrom and August Svenson (duet) - Gluntens vigilans (Wennerberg), undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522250)
    Disc No. 84120
  - Judith Nylander and August Svensson, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522268)
    Disc No. 84131
  - Matilda Jungstedt and Ake Wallgren (duet) - Duett af Escammillo and Carmen, undated; 1 (Box 745, Item barcode 39002126522276)
    Disc No. 84138
  - The Reverie: Rip Van Winkle: Joseph Jefferson, 1898 January 4; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522524)
    Disc No. 699
  - The Statue of Liberty Oration: Chauncey M. Depew, 1898 January 7; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522532)
    Disc No. 694
  - American & Spanish bugle calls no. 4: Emil Cassi, of Roosevelt's Rough Riders, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522508)
    Disc No. 3442
  - The Toast: Rip Van Winkle: Joseph Jefferson, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522516)
    Disc No. 698Z
  - Mon Coeur Chante (My Heart Sings): sung by Miss Marie Tempest, 1901 March 18; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522631)
    Disc No. 3234
  - Fantasia: Arthur Taylor, 1901 March 14; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522649)
    Disc No. 6015
  - Vo Snie Ia Gorko Plakal': [Ich Hab in Traum Geweinet]: Szuman: N. N. Figner, 1912; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522557)
    Disc No. 22667
  - Au Bruit de la Guerrel: chant avec piano: Mlle. Jeannie [Doust?], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522656)
    Disc No. 33126
  - Faust: Scene de l'eglise, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522565)
    Disc No. 32637
  - Ratcatcher's Song, 1899 May 26; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522573)
    Disc No. 40016
  - Haiden Roslein: gesungen von Franz Pacal, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522425)
    Disc No. 42023
  - Bachstelzenlied: Mikado: Sullivan: gesungen von Ewald Bruckner, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522540)
    Disc No. 42494
  - L'immortalita dell'anima: Predica di Padre Agostino, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522433)
    Disc No. 51153
  - Tu Che a Dio: Lucia di Lammermoor: Donizetti: Carlo [Luffetto?], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522581)
    Disc No. 52475
  - Ruy-Blas: Io S'cacciato Io Bandito!: Ferruccio Corradetti, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522599)
    Disc No. 52244
  - La Paloma: Canzorie spagniola: Ferruccio Corradetti, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522441)
    Disc No. 52214
  - Pacliacci: E allor perche di?: Ferruccio Corradetti, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522466)
    Disc No. 52227
  - Bella Figlia di Amore: Rigoletto: Carlo Caffetto, 1900 July; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522458)
    Disc No. 52488
  - La donna è mobile (Rigoletto): Verdi: Carlo Caffetto: Milano, 1900 July 25; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522383)
    Disc No. 52491
  - Mefistofele- Giunto sul passo estremo: Verdi: Carlo Caffetto: Milano, 1900 July 16; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522391)
    Disc No. 52493
  - Pique Dame: What Is Our Life?: Andrei M. Larinsky: St. Petersburg, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522623)
    Disc No. 22337
  - Vechernaia Zviezda (Evening Star): Tangeizer: P. K. Stepanov: St. Petersburg, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522607)
    Disc No. 22416
  - Oh Tu bell'astro incantator: Tannhauser: Coradetti: Milan, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522409)
    Disc No. 52563
  - Vi ravviso o luoghi ameni: La Sonnambula: Bellini: Sig. Franke: Milano, 1900 July 10; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522417)
    Disc No. 52598
  - Ernani involami: Verdi: Grippa: Milano, 1900 August 2; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522474)
  - Se una pudica vergine: Traviata: Adami, Cesarani e Corradetti, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522482)
    Disc No. 54125
  - Africana: [Mamastor] re dell'onde profonde: Corradetti: Coro, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522490)
    Disc No. 54515
  - Coronation Record: God Save the King (male singer with band); 3 cheers, undated; 1; Item not digitized. No center hole; raising disc above spindle causes cartridge to bottom out due to raised edge around the disc. (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002128474286)
    Disc No. 8-51209
  - Noktyurn [Nocturne]; Russain duet by Grodzny [Grozky]: A.M. Labinsky and V.I. Kastorsky: St. Petersburg, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002125667932)
    Disc No. 24033
  - M M Chuprynnikov, N M Safonov, V. I. Dosev, and V.I. Kastorskii: Russian vocal quartet; comic song by Feit: The beetle and the Rose; M.M. Chuprynnikov; N.M. Safonov; V.I. Losev; V.I. Kastorsky; St. Petersburg [The Worm and the Rose], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002125667940)
    Disc No. 2-24311
  - Germania: Franchetti: Emanuele Bucalo, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522664)
    Disc No. 52805
  - Promethesus: Goethe: Josef Kainz, 1902 May 17; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522672)
    Disc No. 41224
  - Arja z opery Boheme III. Akt [La Boheme: Aria, A3]: Puccini: Irene Bohuss, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522680)
    Disc No. 23248
  - Weyla's Gesang [Wolf Song]: Hugo Wolf: Leopold Demuth, k.k. Kammersanger, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522698)
    Disc No. 2-42094
  - Jahrmarktscene: Hugo Bock: Karl Von Zeska, k.u.k. Hofschauspieler, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522706)
    Disc No. 41225
  - Fra Diavolo: Auber: Ferruccio Corradetti, Pianoforte M Cottone, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522714)
    Disc No. 52817
  - Andrea Chenier (Racconto): Giordano: Ernestina Tebro, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522722)
    Disc No. 53131
  - Den gang jeg kun var saa stor som saa (Harrens Vise af Helligtrekongers Aften) P. Heise: Niels Juel Simsonsen, Kgl. Kammersanger, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522730)
    Disc No. 82636
  - Il professore di trombone, A spasso di Cantalamessa, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522748)
    Disc No. 52261X
  - Bedanoondorati - from Sri Krishna; Pauna Lal Sircar [Pannalal Sircar] [Classic Theater, Calcutta], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522755)
    Disc No. 13220
  - The Two Grenadiers: Schumann: D.I. Bukhtoyarov, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522763)
    Disc No. 2-22206
  - Haikeleben: Judischen Quartett, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522771)
    Disc No. 24201
  - Kærlighed paa Grønland: Skuespiller Victor Wulff, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522789)
  - Prazske deti", dvojzpev: Bratři Hartmanove, 1904 March; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522797)
    Disc No. 74063
  - Una lezione di trombone: detta di Fercor [Ferruccio Corradetti], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522813)
    Disc No. 51176
  - Ach Nenu tu, Neni: Arr. Bohm: Josephin Krause [in Czech?], undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522821)
    Disc No. 73013
  - a) Kudy, kudy cestička; b) Vylĕtela holubĕnka ze skály: Maria Klan-Panzner [Malka Bobkova], 1902; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522839)
    Disc No. 73030
  - Má dívenka jak růže jest: Fibich: Ottokar Marak, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522847)
    Disc No. 72749
  - Acqua Azucarillos y Aguardiente- Coro de Barquilleros: Chueca: Artistas de Teatro Eldorado de Barcelona, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522854)
    Disc No. 64543
  - Ballada: Musorgslcago: P.D. Orlov, undated; 1 (Box 745a, Item barcode 39002126522862)
    Disc No. 22136
  - Auld Lang Syne; 42, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522284)
    Disc No. 42
  - Alle Copir-Rechie; 30, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522292)
    Disc No. 30
  - Lord's Prayer; 25, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522300)
    Disc No. 25
  - [unintetlligible]; 4; 35, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522318)
    Disc No. 4,35
  - Blue Bells of Scotland; 50, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522326)
    Disc No. 50
  - [unintelligible], undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522367)
    Disc No. 12
  - Hark! the herald angels sing; 49, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522334)
    Disc No. 49
  - Le Pere La Victoire; 164, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522342)
    Disc No. 164
  - Alle Copir-Rechie, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522375)
    Disc No. 650
  - Instumental-Quintett; Alte Dessauer March de Dessau; 76, undated; 1; 5 inch disc (Box 785, Item barcode 39002126522359)
    Disc No. 376